(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
To everyone on the island.
Cumgratulations!
Cumgrats get pregnant!
Cumgraats!
With the establishment of the New Lewd Law,
a celebratory event
will also be held on Seiran Island.
It's called the Dick Launching Ceremony.
The Guillotine ship will set sail.
And at sea, the ringleader
of the Anti-Copulation Force,
Nanase Katagiri is
scheduled to be executed.
Please come and join us
on the day of the event.
To counter the New Lewd Law,
I've rescheduled Fumino's departure date.
Due to the Dick Launching Ceremony,
the water gate
will be open for a moment.
This is your last chance.
Don't mess up, warriors.
If we fail this,
we'll lose our secret base.
Does this mean we have to accept lewd sex?
At this rate,
Katagiri-san will lose
her chastity in front of everyone.
Nanase-chan...
What do we do?
What do we do, big brother?
At this rate, the XXX's tits
will be purged in a cocoon.
Eh?
Big brother?
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
This is the prefectural governor's office,
when a distinguished guest arrives,
I can use it freely with the authority
of the FS representative.
And you are an exceptionally special guest.
Senpai.
Please rest assured.
Everyone is out preparing
for the Dick Launching Ceremony.
When did you figure it out?
Hmm, maybe from the beginning.
When I make mucous membrane contact,
I can generally
understand the other person.
Give Nanase back.
To do that, why don't we talk first?
Do you think I'll negotiate
after you took away my comrade?
Aren't we also your comrades in FS?
That was my mistake.
It's my half-assed foolishness
for sympathizing with you lot.
Right now, I feel absolutely no sympathy.
I'll crush you along with the ordinance.
How?
We have Fumino on our side.
Can you do it?
To your own senpai?
You think I can't do it?!
Please sit down, senpai.
Now, shall we begin our conversation?
It's true that
I was a little rough with Katagiri-san.
We were backed into a corner ourselves.
FS has been ordered
to cut costs due to financial problems.
The only way to break this situation is...
My dick?
Your dick possesses the divine proportion
of ecstasy, a miracle of nature.
Those pierced by that meat rod...
will lose themselves completely
and drown in pleasure.
Don't be ridiculous.
My dick has no such power.
What is this?
So...
big...
Cumming!
Adding my and
Ikuko's aphrodisiac techniques...
and the coercive power of the guillotine,
what would happen?
That's right. You will have
a king's power that surpasses magic
The power to hold everything
in the palm of your hand.
You are the owner of the King Cock.
Are you planning
to use my dick to start a coup d'état?
A coup d'état?
So that's your true colors.
In the end, you're just going after power.
We just need to maintain our advantage.
Enough power
so that no one can interfere with us.
I don't want to lose FS.
It's for the sake
of saving children like me.
Wata-chan, any sign of him?
Nope, he is nowhere to be found.
Don't tell me my brother was captured too.
Don't worry.
He's not someone
who'd get caught that easily.
- Eh?
- What's that?
I just bought it.
I stopped by the convenience store
while looking for Tachibana-san.
No way he'd be there.
Alright.
Next, I'll look for him in Pervert Land.
I'll go check the beach.
I come from an old,
distinguished family in Kyoto.
Although, we fell into ruin
before I was born.
I was sent away to serve as an apprentice.
Sounds like ancient history, doesn't it?
But I'm very clumsy.
I can't do anything
that a normal person can.
The only thing I'm good at is making tea.
Wherever I went, I was deemed incompetent,
and eventually sold to Seiran Island.
Is that where
you learned the perverted technique?
Well, it's a long time ago.
I barely remember how I lost my virginity.
Eventually, I was noticed by SHO
and came to lead FS.
Compared to other people,
I had a slightly special power.
MINOTSUKI ACADEMY
Only FS gave me a job, a place to live.
And a family to belong to.
They understood me.
In other words, I'm someone...
who can't survive anywhere
but Seiran Island.
There are many children on this island
who have no place to belong.
This is a home where misunderstood children
like me can live in peace.
It is my wish to continue
protecting FS forever.
Stop going on and on with your sob story.
As if you're the only one
with a painful past.
You're the same way, aren't you, Senpai?
What do you mean?
You became XXX because you were bullied
for your dick during childhood, right?
How did you know that?
Cause I'm the student council president.
Even now,
you can't forgive the people
of this island for oppressing you.
That's why you're trying
to crush the Perverted Ordinance.
That's right,
I resent the people of Seiran Island.
Therefore,
I will crush this pervert's paradise and...
you bastards
who control it with peer pressure!
That is the Anti-Copulation Force, NLNS.
So that something
like that will never happen again.
So that I myself
will never make the same mistake
Your anger is not wrong in any way.
If you have made any mistake,
it is only that...
you perceived your own dick as a flaw.
Shut up.
Having a massive dick is not a flaw.
It is part of your charm.
Shut up! What do you...
I want to understand you.
I want to know you so, so much.
I want to know everything about you.
No matter what.
I want you so badly.
Even if you stamp your feet in frustration.
Even if you cry and wail like a child.
This is the first time
I've ever felt this way.
What are you saying?
I want you.
And the world will learn
to worship what I lust for.
If you want to take revenge
on the people of the island,
let's work together.
Let's take revenge on the people who...
cast you aside
and trampled all over you back then.
Let's rule over the people.
Make them correctly understand your power,
your true worth, shall we?
If you choose that path,
you will become the one
who rules over sex, the Sex Emperor.
And you'll reign supreme over the world.
In return,
please keep me by your side forever.
Senpai.
Give Nanase back.
Yes.
Don't lay a hand on the other members.
In exchange,
I'll offer my dick.
Ahh!
I'm happy that you've returned
on your own will, senpai.
Give me some time.
I have one last thing to take care of.
Nukitashi.
INITIALIZING
MEMENTO
Big brother.
What were you doing,
abandoning your precious sister?
Asane-chan was so worried, you know.
She thought you were also captured.
Tachibana-san.
I'm offering my dick to FS.
In exchange for
Nanase's and you guys' safety.
Big brother.
What do you mean "offering?"
That means...
Why you, Tachibana-san!?
Can't you just hand over your dick
and be done with it!?
My dick and I are one and the same.
Inseparable.
If you do that,
you'll have to reveal
your shitty massive dick.
- This is fine.
- Eh?
To hell with my pride!
This happened because I hesitated that day.
So I have to put an end to this
I have to take responsibility.
We won't have
to be afraid of lewd sex anymore.
We can have sex
only with the people we love,
without succumbing to peer pressure.
We've even gotten our revenge.
We of NLNS can now officially disband.
Fumino?
My apologies.
I got it wrong.
Pull yourself together!
Do you think you are...
fighting all alone,
with only yourself and your dick?
A prideful dick's reign is short-lived!
We are friends who can
bare our souls to each other!
We are comrades bound by a strong bond.
Just as you and your dick are inseparable,
so are you and us.
That's right, big brother.
No matter how painful the situation,
no matter how big the complex,
there are people who will
stay by your side and support you.
The one who taught me that...
is the huge dick hanging here.
That is your individuality, Tachibana-kun.
Hah!
How can you just
unilaterally end the fight you started?!
I'm fat.
I can't have sex because
I don't want people to see my stomach.
I'm small and have a baby face!
I look like a loli.
I'm not a loli, though.
Eh?
I'm a shut-in.
I'm not into
any man other than you, brother.
My hair and eye color
are naturally special.
Fumino...
And my breasts are small, and...
Big brother.
We are a minority.
We couldn't fit in.
We were bullied.
We worried, suffered, and got hurt.
Even so, unlike that time,
we have comrades now, right?
Giving up without doing anything
is something only a child would do.
Tachibana-sanm, you're like a dick.
If you go limp,
just get hard again and fight back.
That's right.
Will you all follow me?
That's why this time.
Whatever you desire,
what you believe in, just do it.
Tachibana-san, that is...
Yes, I'm getting hard.
It's arched back so much it hurts.
It's been a while.
I heard it was big, but...
It's kind of divine.
Thank you.
Thanks to everyone...
I finally realized.
I won't be swayed by
any words or thoughts anymore.
I...
Junnosuke Tachibana...
even if it's impossible,
I will obtain what I truly desire.
Guillotine.
That is the symbol
of the Perverted Ordinance.
Forged by the artisans
of Seiran Island with XXXjob,
crafted by hand,
a framework of perversion.
With speed that exceeds 190 km/h,
allowing not even a one-minute deviation.
Truly an insertion
like a flash of lightning.
Those who are penetrated by it will tremble
in ecstasy and cum without exception.
The Dick Launching Ceremony
will climax at...
the sacred waters of 19°45'85" North.
People pray the Japan's
Five Cock for a bountiful harvest,
pierce the defiled XXX that goes against
perversion in a traditional ceremony.
Everyone, please place
your hands on your crotch.
And offer your XXX and your XXX.
That was Kouki Senba,
an expert on Guillotine and dicks.
The town is already enveloped
in a tremendous heat and genitals
Due to the influence
of the recent Coming-of-Sex day,
a large number of islanders
are disguised as Hamedori-kun.
Well-mannered XXX are crowding to get
a glimpse of Nanase Katagiri's execution.
Furthermore,
we heard that a miraculous object
called the magical dick will be unveiled.
Truly the beginning of lewd sex
spreading from Seiran Island to the world.
Everyone, please do not miss this day
that will go down in world history.
How pathetic.
To resist even at this point.
Tell me where your comrades are.
That sullen face will be distorted
with pleasure in a few hours.
The unbreakable chain
unless you have sex detects everything.
Body temperature,
blood pressure, heart rate,
XXX contraction and vitamin deficiencies.
It's the perfect thing to bind you.
It's a guillotine execution
in full public view
Better wash your XXX and wait.
This is for the best.
If there is entertainment
during the ceremony,
we can send Fumino off.
That's not it.
No matter which one I choose...
Jun, as long as you desire...
I will...
Today is a memorable day for Seiran Island.
It will be a day
that decides the future of us FS.
For all of us to survive,
the magical dick is essential.
And what we must defend at all costs...
is the guillotine.
To spread the New Sex Law,
the executive power
of the guillotine is essential.
Noroman-san.
Please don't mistake
the guillotine for the penis, okay?
Eh, are they different things?
Thoroughly guard every area.
Don't miss a single pubic lice.
Even if the Anti-Copulation Force comes...
they can't save Katagiri-san, right?
Not a single bit of confusion
or commotion will be tolerated.
We must not tarnish SHO's honor.
Who is Honor-san?
It's the pillar.
We are comrades bound by a strong bond.
Nothing can ever defeat us.
It seems today will be a day
that isn't even in my data.
So same as always?
Now is the time! Show them the pride of FS!
Sir, yes, sir!
Everyone, to your posts!
Hey, is my beloved
magical dick really coming?
Well, I wonder.
There's only one objective.
Reject FS's offer and rescue Nanase.
That is all.
Roger.
The slap and kick
were very effective.
Thanks to that, I've come to my senses.
I am deeply ashamed.
Can I leave that matter to you?
Leave it all to me.
So in the end,
we're ignoring the secret base's orders.
But I'm glad.
The Flat-Chested Sisters
don't have to disband.
Fumino-chan will probably
graduate soon, though.
Die, you huge tits!
- But loli is cute!
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not a loli!
- For not being able to send you home.
After repeatedly enduring hardships,
overcoming countless difficulties,
at the end of contemplation,
one's wish is fulfilled.
Don't worry, I'm a strong woman.
Wait for me, Nanase.
Ah, just as you said.
I'll do it, this time for sure!
Now, the Dick Launching Ceremony
is about to begin.
10, 9, 8...
The opening is kicked off
with a few fireworks.
It is said to represent the letters SHO,
the symbol of lewdness.
3, 2, 1...
Eh? N-L-N-S?
So that is the answer you've chosen.
Senpai.
Now, The New Hamedori-kun
Mass Outbreak Operation...
commence!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Engage!
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder, have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me